{
    "subject": "resource/Red_Courage",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United States",
    "human_readable": "Red Courage is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9681795835494995,
            "question": "Is Red Courage American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9580307006835938,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Red Courage and the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7763314843177795,
            "question": "Where is Red Courage from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6636312007904053,
            "question": "What country is Red Courage associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6364499926567078,
            "question": "Red Courage is likely from which part of the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.625423014163971,
            "question": "Which country could Red Courage represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6013140082359314,
            "question": "Where might Red Courage be found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5974062085151672,
            "question": "What nationality is Red Courage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4765039384365082,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Red Courage's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4270396828651428,
            "question": "What can you infer about Red Courage based on its origin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Red Courage is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_425_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Red Courage's origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_425_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Red Courage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_425_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Red Courage be found?",
            "html": "dbpedia_425_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_425_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention several facts about \"The Red Badge of Courage\", including its setting (\"set during the American Civil War\"), its author (Stephen Crane), and its themes. None of them contradict the statement \"Red Courage is from United States.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about \"The Red Badge of Courage,\" which was written by Stephen Crane and set during the American Civil War. Therefore, it can be inferred that \"Red Badge\" (likely a reference to \"The Red Badge of Courage\") is indeed from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}